connectwithyourteens.net 2011-08-13

# Privacy Policy

Privacy Policy for http://connectwithyourteens.blogspot.com/

If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us by email at jwag57@gmail.com.

At http://connectwithyourteens.blogspot.com/, the privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information is received and collected by http://connectwithyourteens.blogspot.com/ and how it is used.

**Log Files**  
Like many other Web sites, http://connectwithyourteens.blogspot.com/ makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.

**Cookies and Web Beacons**  
http://connectwithyourteens.blogspot.com/ does not use cookies.

Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include Google Adsense, Amazon, and Kontera.

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on http://connectwithyourteens.blogspot.com/ send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. These companies may use the information outlined above (which does not include your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. These companies often use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [click here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp) (link to the NAI universal user opt-out).

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers' respective websites.
